whatsmode.com 2017-06-23

# Privacy Policy

  * We will not sell, share, trade, or give away any personal information that we receive regarding our customers. We are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect about you to process orders and to provide a more personalized shopping experience. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.

  * ### WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

### HOW DO WE USE IT?

We collect the domain name of e-mail addresses of visitors to our site and aggregate (not personally identifiable) information on what pages visitors access. We use this information to monitor the use of the site and to improve its performance and usefulness. We also collect information you volunteer, such as survey responses, comments, purchasing and billing information, and your requests.

When you order, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, contact telephone number, credit card number, and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status.

We may also use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to the Web site, new services, and special offers we think you’ll find valuable.

  * ### HOW DO WE PROTECT CUSTOMER INFORMATION?

When you place orders or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access.

  * ### HOW DO WE ALLOW CUSTOMERS TO UPDATE OR CHANGE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT?

You may update or change information related to your account by updating your profile, accessible via the home page once you are logged in, or by sending us email. Yes, we do use cookies, however we do not overuse them. We use cookies to enhance your shopping and browsing experience. The text in a cookie, by itself, only tells us that you have visited our site before. It does not store any personal information such as your name, e-mail address, street address, or phone number. Cookies are also used to maintain your shopping basket. All data contained in the shopping basked is kept on our server and not in the cookie your machine is assigned.

  * ### YOUR CONSENT

By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of this information. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

  * ### TELL US WHAT YOU THINK

We welcome your questions and comments about privacy. If you have any questions, please email us.
